# **DAVID TREJOS**

(+57) 3156616275 • davidtrejoscortes@gmail.com • davidtrejos.vercel.app

## **PROFILE**

System engineer and software developer passionate about continuous learning, developing creative solutions and improving code quality. with experience in Java and NodeJS for the backend, Angular and React for the frontend, plus React Native for building mobile apps.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

CR CARS Ene 2021 - Dic 2021

 I worked as a Software Developer, creating the backend for a dealership's web application, ensuring seamless integration with its mobile version while collaborating closely with the development team.

APPSLIFE Ene 2022 - Dic 2022

• I worked as a Java Developer for one year, where I was responsible for developing web and mobile applications from the backend. My role involved designing and implementing server-side logic, optimizing database interactions, and ensuring seamless integration with front-end components to deliver efficient and user-friendly applications.

ACCENTURE Ene 2023 - Jul 2023

• Professional internship as a web developer supporting the digital web channel of a multinational energy company that requested Accenture's services. During this time I did support in the field of software development especially on the back side and some tasks on the front side.

## **360 MARKETING SERVICES**

Ago 2023 - Abr 2024

 I provided my services as a software developer for a self-management portal of a Colombian bank. Here I took care of all kinds of back and front-end requirements. I worked with java the microservices part and in Angular the interaction and creation of different components. Here I was also in charge of unit testing the entire portal on both fronts. For the back I implemented them with Junit & Mockito and for the front with Karma & Jazmine.

## **EDUCATION**

SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

Sep 2017 - Sep 2024

University of Quindío

SOCIAL COMUNICATION

Aug 2009 - Sep 2014

University of Quindío

## ADITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Software development.
- **Programming language:** Java, Python.
- Librarys/Frameworks: Angular, React Js, React Native, Junit, Mockito, Karma, Jazmine.
- Databases: Mysql, MongoDB, PostgresSql.
- Plattforms: AWS, Vercel, Azure.